Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXXII is arranged in 14 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXXII. FINANCIAL ASSISTANCE TO MEMBERS
  - Sub-Series 263-0. Disaster Relief and Financial Assistance to Members
    - Contributions, 1966 (Box 223, Folder 16)
    - Contributions, 1964-1965 (Box 223, Folder 17)
      February 1964-65.
    - General, 1962-1964 (Box 223, Folder 18)
      1962-January 1964.
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 223, Folder 19)
      March 16, 1961-62.
    - General, 1959-1960 (Box 223, Folder 20)
    - General, 1957-1961 (Box 223, Folder 21)
      September 1957-March 15, 1961.
    - General, 1955-1957 (Box 223, Folder 22)
      1955-August 1957.
    - General, 1948-1954 (Box 223, Folder 23)
    - Missouri-Kansas Flood, 1952 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Missouri-Kansas Flood, 1951 (Box 224, Folder 2)
      August-December 1951.
    - Missouri-Kansas Flood: Questionnaires, 1951-1952 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Missouri-Kansas Flood: Questionnaires, 1951 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Missouri-Kansas Flood: Questionnaires, 1951 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Missouri-Kansas Flood: Questionnaires, 1951-1952 (Box 224, Folder 6)
    - Financial Assistance to Machinists, 1925 (Box 224, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 263-1 to 263-25. Financial Assistance to Local Members
    - General, 1925 (Box 224, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 263-26. Financial Assistance to Members
    - Florida Hurricane Assistance, 1927 (Box 224, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 263-27. Financial Assistance to Members
    - Florida Hurricane Assistance, 1927 (Box 224, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 263-28. Financial Assistance to Members
    - Mississippi Valley Flood Relief, 1927 (Box 224, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 263-29. Financial Assistance to Members
    - New England Flood Relief, 1928 (Box 224, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 263-30 to 263-35. Financial Assistance to Members
    - New England Flood Relief, 1927-1928 (Box 224, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 263-36. Financial Assistance to Members
    - Eastern Kentucky Flood Relief, 1929 (Box 224, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 263-37 to 263-47. Financial Assistance to Members
    - General, 1931-1934 (Box 224, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 263-48. Financial Assistance to Flood Sufferers
    - General, 1936-1938 (Box 224, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 263-49. Financial Assistance to Ohio Valley Flood Sufferers
    - General, 1937 (Box 224, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 263-50. Financial Assistance to Oklahoma and Texas Tornado Sufferers
    - General, 1947 (Box 224, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 263-51. Financial Assistance to Members
    - Texas City Disaster, Texas City, Texas, 1947-1948 (Box 224, Folder 19)
    - Texas City Disaster, Texas City, Texas, 1947 (Box 224, Folder 20)
      1947 April
  - Sub-Series 263-52. Financial Assistance to Members
    - Frederick O. Withers, 1948-1949 (Box 224, Folder 21)